{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957650308","data":{"timestamp":" 946957650308"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957651488","data":{"timestamp":" 946957651487"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957652386","data":{"timestamp":" 946957652385"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957653474","data":{"timestamp":" 946957653474"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957654495","data":{"timestamp":" 946957654494"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957655364","data":{"timestamp":" 946957655363"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957656473","data":{"timestamp":" 946957656473"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957657140","data":{"timestamp":" 946957657140"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957658437","data":{"timestamp":" 946957658437"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957660901","data":{"timestamp":" 946957660900"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957661093","data":{"timestamp":" 946957661093"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957662072","data":{"timestamp":" 946957662072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957663451","data":{"timestamp":" 946957663450"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957663600","data":{"timestamp":" 946957663599"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957664756","data":{"timestamp":" 946957664755"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957665416","data":{"timestamp":" 946957665415"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957666515","data":{"timestamp":" 946957666514"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957667313","data":{"timestamp":" 946957667312"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957667431","data":{"timestamp":" 946957667431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957668129","data":{"timestamp":" 946957668129"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" MTENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957671113","data":{"timestamp":" 946957671112"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957671983","data":{"timestamp":" 946957671982"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957672216","data":{"timestamp":" 946957672216"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957672844","data":{"timestamp":" 946957672844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957672958","data":{"timestamp":" 946957672958"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957673967","data":{"timestamp":" 946957673966"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957674877","data":{"timestamp":" 946957674876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957675561","data":{"timestamp":" 946957675561"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957676838","data":{"timestamp":" 946957676838"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" CHANIKIWITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957679448","data":{"timestamp":" 946957679447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957680491","data":{"timestamp":" 946957680491"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957680695","data":{"timestamp":" 946957680695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957681413","data":{"timestamp":" 946957681412"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" MIKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957682407","data":{"timestamp":" 946957682407"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" MINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957683392","data":{"timestamp":" 946957683392"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957684126","data":{"timestamp":" 946957684126"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957684726","data":{"timestamp":" 946957684725"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957685571","data":{"timestamp":" 946957685571"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957686075","data":{"timestamp":" 946957686075"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957686909","data":{"timestamp":" 946957686909"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957690479","data":{"timestamp":" 946957690479"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957691152","data":{"timestamp":" 946957691152"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957691946","data":{"timestamp":" 946957691946"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957693084","data":{"timestamp":" 946957693084"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957693740","data":{"timestamp":" 946957693740"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957694396","data":{"timestamp":" 946957694395"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957695107","data":{"timestamp":" 946957695106"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957696022","data":{"timestamp":" 946957696021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957696895","data":{"timestamp":" 946957696895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957697129","data":{"timestamp":" 946957697129"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957698414","data":{"timestamp":" 946957698414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ILIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957699014","data":{"timestamp":" 946957699013"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957701666","data":{"timestamp":" 946957701666"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957702000","data":{"timestamp":" 946957702000"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957702747","data":{"timestamp":" 946957702746"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" NGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957704391","data":{"timestamp":" 946957704390"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957704865","data":{"timestamp":" 946957704864"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957705378","data":{"timestamp":" 946957705377"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957705871","data":{"timestamp":" 946957705871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957709004","data":{"timestamp":" 946957709004"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957709657","data":{"timestamp":" 946957709657"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957711114","data":{"timestamp":" 946957711113"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" HAKUWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957711729","data":{"timestamp":" 946957711729"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957712316","data":{"timestamp":" 946957712316"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957712995","data":{"timestamp":" 946957712995"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957713420","data":{"timestamp":" 946957713420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957714429","data":{"timestamp":" 946957714428"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957717527","data":{"timestamp":" 946957717526"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957718524","data":{"timestamp":" 946957718524"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957719532","data":{"timestamp":" 946957719531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957720057","data":{"timestamp":" 946957720057"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957720240","data":{"timestamp":" 946957720240"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957721464","data":{"timestamp":" 946957721464"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957722868","data":{"timestamp":" 946957722868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAMKINGA"," userResponse":" UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957723111","data":{"timestamp":" 946957723111"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957724235","data":{"timestamp":" 946957724234"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957724798","data":{"timestamp":" 946957724798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" YOYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957727805","data":{"timestamp":" 946957727805"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957728771","data":{"timestamp":" 946957728771"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957729508","data":{"timestamp":" 946957729507"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957730415","data":{"timestamp":" 946957730414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957733464","data":{"timestamp":" 946957733464"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957734217","data":{"timestamp":" 946957734217"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957734900","data":{"timestamp":" 946957734900"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957735614","data":{"timestamp":" 946957735614"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957735858","data":{"timestamp":" 946957735857"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957736581","data":{"timestamp":" 946957736581"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957737965","data":{"timestamp":" 946957737965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957741233","data":{"timestamp":" 946957741233"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957742016","data":{"timestamp":" 946957742016"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957742792","data":{"timestamp":" 946957742791"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957742983","data":{"timestamp":" 946957742983"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957744007","data":{"timestamp":" 946957744006"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957744842","data":{"timestamp":" 946957744841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957747199","data":{"timestamp":" 946957747199"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957747442","data":{"timestamp":" 946957747442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957748121","data":{"timestamp":" 946957748121"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957749211","data":{"timestamp":" 946957749211"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957750235","data":{"timestamp":" 946957750234"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" KUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957750769","data":{"timestamp":" 946957750768"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957751448","data":{"timestamp":" 946957751447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957751643","data":{"timestamp":" 946957751643"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957752326","data":{"timestamp":" 946957752326"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957752519","data":{"timestamp":" 946957752519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957753403","data":{"timestamp":" 946957753403"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957756256","data":{"timestamp":" 946957756255"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957756871","data":{"timestamp":" 946957756870"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957757738","data":{"timestamp":" 946957757737"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957758543","data":{"timestamp":" 946957758542"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957758767","data":{"timestamp":" 946957758766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957759415","data":{"timestamp":" 946957759414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAHATI"," userResponse":" BAHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957759860","data":{"timestamp":" 946957759859"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957762909","data":{"timestamp":" 946957762909"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957763735","data":{"timestamp":" 946957763734"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957764251","data":{"timestamp":" 946957764251"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957764516","data":{"timestamp":" 946957764515"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957765242","data":{"timestamp":" 946957765242"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957765484","data":{"timestamp":" 946957765483"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957766692","data":{"timestamp":" 946957766691"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957767491","data":{"timestamp":" 946957767490"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957768360","data":{"timestamp":" 946957768360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957768866","data":{"timestamp":" 946957768866"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957772178","data":{"timestamp":" 946957772178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOTELEA"," userResponse":" ALIPOTELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957773366","data":{"timestamp":" 946957773365"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957775953","data":{"timestamp":" 946957775952"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957777498","data":{"timestamp":" 946957777497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957780961","data":{"timestamp":" 946957780960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKETI"," userResponse":" ALIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957781538","data":{"timestamp":" 946957781537"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957781664","data":{"timestamp":" 946957781664"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957782109","data":{"timestamp":" 946957782108"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957782355","data":{"timestamp":" 946957782355"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957783091","data":{"timestamp":" 946957783090"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EDOME"," userResponse":" EDOME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957784416","data":{"timestamp":" 946957784415"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" KUSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957785585","data":{"timestamp":" 946957785584"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957787936","data":{"timestamp":" 946957787935"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957788583","data":{"timestamp":" 946957788582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957789622","data":{"timestamp":" 946957789621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957790808","data":{"timestamp":" 946957790807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957791043","data":{"timestamp":" 946957791042"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957791832","data":{"timestamp":" 946957791831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOTA"," userResponse":" KUOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957792472","data":{"timestamp":" 946957792471"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957795423","data":{"timestamp":" 946957795423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957795958","data":{"timestamp":" 946957795958"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957796608","data":{"timestamp":" 946957796607"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957797716","data":{"timestamp":" 946957797715"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957799114","data":{"timestamp":" 946957799113"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957800013","data":{"timestamp":" 946957800012"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957800510","data":{"timestamp":" 946957800509"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957801138","data":{"timestamp":" 946957801138"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957801597","data":{"timestamp":" 946957801596"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957802446","data":{"timestamp":" 946957802445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957805089","data":{"timestamp":" 946957805089"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957806537","data":{"timestamp":" 946957806537"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFANANA"," userResponse":" ALIYEFANANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957806737","data":{"timestamp":" 946957806737"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957807936","data":{"timestamp":" 946957807936"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957808904","data":{"timestamp":" 946957808904"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957810133","data":{"timestamp":" 946957810133"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMCHUNGA"," userResponse":" AKIMCHUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957812977","data":{"timestamp":" 946957812977"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957813654","data":{"timestamp":" 946957813654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957815345","data":{"timestamp":" 946957815344"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITABASAMU"," userResponse":" ALITABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957815964","data":{"timestamp":" 946957815963"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957816586","data":{"timestamp":" 946957816586"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957817304","data":{"timestamp":" 946957817304"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957818354","data":{"timestamp":" 946957818353"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957818621","data":{"timestamp":" 946957818620"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957819321","data":{"timestamp":" 946957819321"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957819518","data":{"timestamp":" 946957819517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957820227","data":{"timestamp":" 946957820226"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957822644","data":{"timestamp":" 946957822643"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957824294","data":{"timestamp":" 946957824293"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," userResponse":" ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957825034","data":{"timestamp":" 946957825032"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957825440","data":{"timestamp":" 946957825440"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957826309","data":{"timestamp":" 946957826309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" KUCHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957827090","data":{"timestamp":" 946957827089"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957827769","data":{"timestamp":" 946957827769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957829137","data":{"timestamp":" 946957829137"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957832125","data":{"timestamp":" 946957832124"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957833511","data":{"timestamp":" 946957833510"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYAFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIYAFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957834033","data":{"timestamp":" 946957834033"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957834581","data":{"timestamp":" 946957834579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957835186","data":{"timestamp":" 946957835186"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957836393","data":{"timestamp":" 946957836393"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957839634","data":{"timestamp":" 946957839634"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOANGALIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957840251","data":{"timestamp":" 946957840251"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957841728","data":{"timestamp":" 946957841727"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957842200","data":{"timestamp":" 946957842199"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957842705","data":{"timestamp":" 946957842705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957843119","data":{"timestamp":" 946957843119"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957843713","data":{"timestamp":" 946957843712"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957843797","data":{"timestamp":" 946957843797"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957844347","data":{"timestamp":" 946957844346"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957845808","data":{"timestamp":" 946957845807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957846779","data":{"timestamp":" 946957846778"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMETULIA"," userResponse":" AMETULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957847250","data":{"timestamp":" 946957847250"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957847872","data":{"timestamp":" 946957847872"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957850714","data":{"timestamp":" 946957850714"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957852300","data":{"timestamp":" 946957852299"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957853186","data":{"timestamp":" 946957853185"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957853750","data":{"timestamp":" 946957853750"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957855137","data":{"timestamp":" 946957855136"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPAPATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957855755","data":{"timestamp":" 946957855755"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957856344","data":{"timestamp":" 946957856344"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957857253","data":{"timestamp":" 946957857252"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957858406","data":{"timestamp":" 946957858406"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWONGOZEA"," userResponse":" AKAMWONGOZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957859216","data":{"timestamp":" 946957859215"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957859847","data":{"timestamp":" 946957859846"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957861056","data":{"timestamp":" 946957861055"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 6be9a32e-bb14-4e88-83eb-27be9b1953e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959306986","data":{"timestamp":" 946959306986"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959307981","data":{"timestamp":" 946959307981"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959308172","data":{"timestamp":" 946959308172"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959308819","data":{"timestamp":" 946959308818"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959309384","data":{"timestamp":" 946959309383"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959309868","data":{"timestamp":" 946959309868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959310293","data":{"timestamp":" 946959310292"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959310736","data":{"timestamp":" 946959310736"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959310909","data":{"timestamp":" 946959310908"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959311482","data":{"timestamp":" 946959311482"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959311967","data":{"timestamp":" 946959311967"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" MINNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959314726","data":{"timestamp":" 946959314726"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959315289","data":{"timestamp":" 946959315289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959315812","data":{"timestamp":" 946959315812"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959316026","data":{"timestamp":" 946959316026"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959316409","data":{"timestamp":" 946959316409"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959317196","data":{"timestamp":" 946959317195"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959319520","data":{"timestamp":" 946959319520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959319964","data":{"timestamp":" 946959319963"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959320157","data":{"timestamp":" 946959320157"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959320913","data":{"timestamp":" 946959320912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959321768","data":{"timestamp":" 946959321767"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959322233","data":{"timestamp":" 946959322232"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959322399","data":{"timestamp":" 946959322399"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959323028","data":{"timestamp":" 946959323027"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFU"," userResponse":" SAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959323144","data":{"timestamp":" 946959323144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959323668","data":{"timestamp":" 946959323668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959325047","data":{"timestamp":" 946959325046"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959328335","data":{"timestamp":" 946959328334"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959329206","data":{"timestamp":" 946959329205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959329450","data":{"timestamp":" 946959329449"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959329943","data":{"timestamp":" 946959329943"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959330119","data":{"timestamp":" 946959330118"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959330676","data":{"timestamp":" 946959330675"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959331446","data":{"timestamp":" 946959331444"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITATU"," userResponse":" MITATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959332866","data":{"timestamp":" 946959332865"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959333372","data":{"timestamp":" 946959333371"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959334396","data":{"timestamp":" 946959334396"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOTEZA"," userResponse":" KUPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959334991","data":{"timestamp":" 946959334991"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWEZO"," userResponse":" UWEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959335178","data":{"timestamp":" 946959335178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959335847","data":{"timestamp":" 946959335847"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959338411","data":{"timestamp":" 946959338411"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959339005","data":{"timestamp":" 946959339005"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959339815","data":{"timestamp":" 946959339814"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959340475","data":{"timestamp":" 946959340475"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959340948","data":{"timestamp":" 946959340948"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959341864","data":{"timestamp":" 946959341864"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TALANTA"," userResponse":" TALANTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959345043","data":{"timestamp":" 946959345042"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959345892","data":{"timestamp":" 946959345891"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITENDA"," userResponse":" ALITENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959346363","data":{"timestamp":" 946959346363"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959347313","data":{"timestamp":" 946959347312"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959348140","data":{"timestamp":" 946959348140"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959348897","data":{"timestamp":" 946959348896"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959349453","data":{"timestamp":" 946959349452"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959349689","data":{"timestamp":" 946959349688"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959350074","data":{"timestamp":" 946959350074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959350632","data":{"timestamp":" 946959350631"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959351839","data":{"timestamp":" 946959351839"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959352539","data":{"timestamp":" 946959352538"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959354447","data":{"timestamp":" 946959354446"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959355213","data":{"timestamp":" 946959355213"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFANO"," userResponse":" MFANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959356180","data":{"timestamp":" 946959356180"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959356818","data":{"timestamp":" 946959356817"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKETI"," userResponse":" KUKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959356995","data":{"timestamp":" 946959356994"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959357387","data":{"timestamp":" 946959357386"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959358024","data":{"timestamp":" 946959358023"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZIMA"," userResponse":" WAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959358515","data":{"timestamp":" 946959358514"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959359354","data":{"timestamp":" 946959359353"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJADILI"," userResponse":" KUJADILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959359794","data":{"timestamp":" 946959359794"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959360418","data":{"timestamp":" 946959360417"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHIMU"," userResponse":" MUHIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959363356","data":{"timestamp":" 946959363355"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959363556","data":{"timestamp":" 946959363556"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959364143","data":{"timestamp":" 946959364142"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959364991","data":{"timestamp":" 946959364990"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959365623","data":{"timestamp":" 946959365622"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959366362","data":{"timestamp":" 946959366361"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959366759","data":{"timestamp":" 946959366758"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959366945","data":{"timestamp":" 946959366945"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959367331","data":{"timestamp":" 946959367331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959368090","data":{"timestamp":" 946959368089"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959371034","data":{"timestamp":" 946959371033"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" WALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959371910","data":{"timestamp":" 946959371909"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959372649","data":{"timestamp":" 946959372648"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959372891","data":{"timestamp":" 946959372890"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959373593","data":{"timestamp":" 946959373593"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959374069","data":{"timestamp":" 946959374068"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959374716","data":{"timestamp":" 946959374715"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959375413","data":{"timestamp":" 946959375412"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959377960","data":{"timestamp":" 946959377960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959378731","data":{"timestamp":" 946959378731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959378935","data":{"timestamp":" 946959378934"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959379320","data":{"timestamp":" 946959379319"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959379753","data":{"timestamp":" 946959379752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959380246","data":{"timestamp":" 946959380245"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959383248","data":{"timestamp":" 946959383247"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959384174","data":{"timestamp":" 946959384173"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959384943","data":{"timestamp":" 946959384941"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959385769","data":{"timestamp":" 946959385768"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959386423","data":{"timestamp":" 946959386422"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959388843","data":{"timestamp":" 946959388841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959389463","data":{"timestamp":" 946959389462"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959390421","data":{"timestamp":" 946959390421"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959391463","data":{"timestamp":" 946959391463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959392641","data":{"timestamp":" 946959392640"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959393960","data":{"timestamp":" 946959393960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" UNAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959394325","data":{"timestamp":" 946959394324"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959394883","data":{"timestamp":" 946959394882"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959395409","data":{"timestamp":" 946959395408"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959396325","data":{"timestamp":" 946959396324"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959399431","data":{"timestamp":" 946959399431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959400708","data":{"timestamp":" 946959400707"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959401526","data":{"timestamp":" 946959401526"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAKUJA"," userResponse":" ZINAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959401820","data":{"timestamp":" 946959401819"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959402607","data":{"timestamp":" 946959402606"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959405446","data":{"timestamp":" 946959405445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZISIKIA"," userResponse":" NAZISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959406141","data":{"timestamp":" 946959406141"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWANI"," userResponse":" KICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959406785","data":{"timestamp":" 946959406784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959407432","data":{"timestamp":" 946959407431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959408468","data":{"timestamp":" 946959408467"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZIIMBA"," userResponse":" NAZIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959411772","data":{"timestamp":" 946959411771"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959412805","data":{"timestamp":" 946959412805"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959413709","data":{"timestamp":" 946959413709"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959414242","data":{"timestamp":" 946959414242"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959414975","data":{"timestamp":" 946959414975"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959415898","data":{"timestamp":" 946959415898"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959416780","data":{"timestamp":" 946959416780"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOHISI"," userResponse":" ALIPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959417313","data":{"timestamp":" 946959417313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959419940","data":{"timestamp":" 946959419940"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959421242","data":{"timestamp":" 946959421242"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959422195","data":{"timestamp":" 946959422195"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959423165","data":{"timestamp":" 946959423165"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959424429","data":{"timestamp":" 946959424429"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIOUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959425143","data":{"timestamp":" 946959425143"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959427610","data":{"timestamp":" 946959427610"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959428452","data":{"timestamp":" 946959428452"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959429520","data":{"timestamp":" 946959429520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUATIA"," userResponse":" KUFUATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959429814","data":{"timestamp":" 946959429814"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959430368","data":{"timestamp":" 946959430368"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959430831","data":{"timestamp":" 946959430831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959431767","data":{"timestamp":" 946959431766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959434936","data":{"timestamp":" 946959434935"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959435492","data":{"timestamp":" 946959435492"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959435970","data":{"timestamp":" 946959435969"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959436136","data":{"timestamp":" 946959436136"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959436914","data":{"timestamp":" 946959436914"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959437890","data":{"timestamp":" 946959437889"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959438647","data":{"timestamp":" 946959438647"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959439234","data":{"timestamp":" 946959439233"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959440057","data":{"timestamp":" 946959440057"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ANGEMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959442556","data":{"timestamp":" 946959442555"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959443682","data":{"timestamp":" 946959443682"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUBALI"," userResponse":" ANGEKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959444259","data":{"timestamp":" 946959444258"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959444976","data":{"timestamp":" 946959444976"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959445490","data":{"timestamp":" 946959445490"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959446236","data":{"timestamp":" 946959446236"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959449153","data":{"timestamp":" 946959449153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959449861","data":{"timestamp":" 946959449860"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959450604","data":{"timestamp":" 946959450603"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959450968","data":{"timestamp":" 946959450967"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959451774","data":{"timestamp":" 946959451774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" WALIPORUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959452605","data":{"timestamp":" 946959452604"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959453765","data":{"timestamp":" 946959453764"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959454586","data":{"timestamp":" 946959454585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959455142","data":{"timestamp":" 946959455142"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959457819","data":{"timestamp":" 946959457819"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959458527","data":{"timestamp":" 946959458526"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959459134","data":{"timestamp":" 946959459134"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959459924","data":{"timestamp":" 946959459924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959460624","data":{"timestamp":" 946959460623"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959460819","data":{"timestamp":" 946959460819"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959461265","data":{"timestamp":" 946959461264"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959461778","data":{"timestamp":" 946959461778"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959464509","data":{"timestamp":" 946959464509"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959464882","data":{"timestamp":" 946959464882"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959465697","data":{"timestamp":" 946959465697"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959466511","data":{"timestamp":" 946959466511"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959467289","data":{"timestamp":" 946959467289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959469846","data":{"timestamp":" 946959469845"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959470662","data":{"timestamp":" 946959470662"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959473218","data":{"timestamp":" 946959473217"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959474075","data":{"timestamp":" 946959474074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959474671","data":{"timestamp":" 946959474671"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959475361","data":{"timestamp":" 946959475359"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959475526","data":{"timestamp":" 946959475526"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959475885","data":{"timestamp":" 946959475884"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959476703","data":{"timestamp":" 946959476702"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959477516","data":{"timestamp":" 946959477516"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959478370","data":{"timestamp":" 946959478370"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" AMEPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959480911","data":{"timestamp":" 946959480911"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959481555","data":{"timestamp":" 946959481554"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959482057","data":{"timestamp":" 946959482057"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959483440","data":{"timestamp":" 946959483440"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959484004","data":{"timestamp":" 946959484004"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959484617","data":{"timestamp":" 946959484617"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959484990","data":{"timestamp":" 946959484990"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959485843","data":{"timestamp":" 946959485843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPWEKE"," userResponse":" UPWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959486667","data":{"timestamp":" 946959486667"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959489748","data":{"timestamp":" 946959489748"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959490925","data":{"timestamp":" 946959490924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959493346","data":{"timestamp":" 946959493345"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959494309","data":{"timestamp":" 946959494308"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ATAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959494922","data":{"timestamp":" 946959494921"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959495785","data":{"timestamp":" 946959495785"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959496625","data":{"timestamp":" 946959496625"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959497150","data":{"timestamp":" 946959497150"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959497636","data":{"timestamp":" 946959497635"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959500405","data":{"timestamp":" 946959500404"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959500929","data":{"timestamp":" 946959500929"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959501442","data":{"timestamp":" 946959501441"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959502575","data":{"timestamp":" 946959502575"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIDHARAU"," userResponse":" WALIDHARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959503118","data":{"timestamp":" 946959503118"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959503571","data":{"timestamp":" 946959503571"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959505996","data":{"timestamp":" 946959505996"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959506209","data":{"timestamp":" 946959506209"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959507392","data":{"timestamp":" 946959507392"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959509676","data":{"timestamp":" 946959509676"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959509859","data":{"timestamp":" 946959509859"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959510572","data":{"timestamp":" 946959510572"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959511645","data":{"timestamp":" 946959511645"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYEONA"," userResponse":" ASIYEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959514450","data":{"timestamp":" 946959514450"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNADHANI"," userResponse":" UNADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959514853","data":{"timestamp":" 946959514853"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959515185","data":{"timestamp":" 946959515185"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959516198","data":{"timestamp":" 946959516198"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAMSAIDIA"," userResponse":" UTAMSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959519249","data":{"timestamp":" 946959519249"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959519873","data":{"timestamp":" 946959519873"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959520590","data":{"timestamp":" 946959520590"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959521405","data":{"timestamp":" 946959521405"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUKATA"," userResponse":" HAKUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959521960","data":{"timestamp":" 946959521960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959524053","data":{"timestamp":" 946959524053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959524426","data":{"timestamp":" 946959524426"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959524819","data":{"timestamp":" 946959524819"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959525331","data":{"timestamp":" 946959525331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959525715","data":{"timestamp":" 946959525715"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959526188","data":{"timestamp":" 946959526188"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959527181","data":{"timestamp":" 946959527181"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959527764","data":{"timestamp":" 946959527764"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOYO"," userResponse":" MOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959530419","data":{"timestamp":" 946959530419"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959531402","data":{"timestamp":" 946959531402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959531555","data":{"timestamp":" 946959531554"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959532358","data":{"timestamp":" 946959532358"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959533582","data":{"timestamp":" 946959533582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNITULIZA"," userResponse":" HUNITULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959534015","data":{"timestamp":" 946959534015"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959534529","data":{"timestamp":" 946959534529"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959534723","data":{"timestamp":" 946959534723"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959535246","data":{"timestamp":" 946959535245"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959538596","data":{"timestamp":" 946959538595"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAMTULIZA"," userResponse":" ZITAMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959539562","data":{"timestamp":" 946959539561"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959539799","data":{"timestamp":" 946959539799"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959540039","data":{"timestamp":" 946959540039"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959543345","data":{"timestamp":" 946959543344"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959544412","data":{"timestamp":" 946959544412"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959545336","data":{"timestamp":" 946959545336"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959546314","data":{"timestamp":" 946959546313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959546722","data":{"timestamp":" 946959546722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959547266","data":{"timestamp":" 946959547266"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959548729","data":{"timestamp":" 946959548729"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMWELEKEZE"," userResponse":" AMWELEKEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959549383","data":{"timestamp":" 946959549383"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959549776","data":{"timestamp":" 946959549776"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959550160","data":{"timestamp":" 946959550160"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959550353","data":{"timestamp":" 946959550353"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959550736","data":{"timestamp":" 946959550735"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959551449","data":{"timestamp":" 946959551449"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959554849","data":{"timestamp":" 946959554849"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959555421","data":{"timestamp":" 946959555421"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959555516","data":{"timestamp":" 946959555516"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959556109","data":{"timestamp":" 946959556109"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959556652","data":{"timestamp":" 946959556652"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959557155","data":{"timestamp":" 946959557155"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959557769","data":{"timestamp":" 946959557769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959558362","data":{"timestamp":" 946959558361"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959558815","data":{"timestamp":" 946959558814"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959559408","data":{"timestamp":" 946959559407"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959560461","data":{"timestamp":" 946959560461"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIOUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959562751","data":{"timestamp":" 946959562751"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959563414","data":{"timestamp":" 946959563414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959564287","data":{"timestamp":" 946959564287"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959564549","data":{"timestamp":" 946959564549"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959565023","data":{"timestamp":" 946959565022"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959565866","data":{"timestamp":" 946959565866"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959566809","data":{"timestamp":" 946959566809"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIANZA"," userResponse":" KILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959567833","data":{"timestamp":" 946959567833"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959568516","data":{"timestamp":" 946959568516"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959569168","data":{"timestamp":" 946959569168"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959572187","data":{"timestamp":" 946959572186"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAFANYI"," userResponse":" WAFANYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959572720","data":{"timestamp":" 946959572720"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959573443","data":{"timestamp":" 946959573443"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959574445","data":{"timestamp":" 946959574445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959574979","data":{"timestamp":" 946959574979"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959575582","data":{"timestamp":" 946959575582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959576526","data":{"timestamp":" 946959576525"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIZOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIZOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959577339","data":{"timestamp":" 946959577339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959580785","data":{"timestamp":" 946959580785"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKILIZA"," userResponse":" WALISIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959581379","data":{"timestamp":" 946959581378"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959582402","data":{"timestamp":" 946959582402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTAMU"," userResponse":" MTAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959582544","data":{"timestamp":" 946959582544"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959583238","data":{"timestamp":" 946959583238"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959585659","data":{"timestamp":" 946959585659"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959586356","data":{"timestamp":" 946959586356"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959587224","data":{"timestamp":" 946959587224"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959587806","data":{"timestamp":" 946959587805"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959588577","data":{"timestamp":" 946959588577"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959589886","data":{"timestamp":" 946959589885"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959590919","data":{"timestamp":" 946959590918"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFAULU"," userResponse":" ALIYEFAULU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959591697","data":{"timestamp":" 946959591696"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959592182","data":{"timestamp":" 946959592182"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959594766","data":{"timestamp":" 946959594765"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959595443","data":{"timestamp":" 946959595442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959595957","data":{"timestamp":" 946959595957"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959596826","data":{"timestamp":" 946959596826"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYEONA"," userResponse":" ASIYEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959597690","data":{"timestamp":" 946959597690"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAWEZA"," userResponse":" ATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959598833","data":{"timestamp":" 946959598833"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959601913","data":{"timestamp":" 946959601912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959602968","data":{"timestamp":" 946959602967"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKAMILISHA"," userResponse":" ALIKAMILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959603513","data":{"timestamp":" 946959603513"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959603857","data":{"timestamp":" 946959603856"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959604410","data":{"timestamp":" 946959604409"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959605506","data":{"timestamp":" 946959605506"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959606296","data":{"timestamp":" 946959606295"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959609232","data":{"timestamp":" 946959609232"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959609497","data":{"timestamp":" 946959609497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959610159","data":{"timestamp":" 946959610158"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959610779","data":{"timestamp":" 946959610778"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKA"," userResponse":" ALITOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959611144","data":{"timestamp":" 946959611143"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959611619","data":{"timestamp":" 946959611619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959612256","data":{"timestamp":" 946959612256"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959612422","data":{"timestamp":" 946959612421"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959613039","data":{"timestamp":" 946959613038"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959614643","data":{"timestamp":" 946959614643"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959615447","data":{"timestamp":" 946959615447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959616135","data":{"timestamp":" 946959616135"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959619048","data":{"timestamp":" 946959619048"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959619290","data":{"timestamp":" 946959619289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959619682","data":{"timestamp":" 946959619681"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959620849","data":{"timestamp":" 946959620849"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959621388","data":{"timestamp":" 946959621387"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959622135","data":{"timestamp":" 946959622134"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUJA"," userResponse":" WALIKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959622705","data":{"timestamp":" 946959622704"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959623542","data":{"timestamp":" 946959623542"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEMBEBA"," userResponse":" WAMEMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959624016","data":{"timestamp":" 946959624015"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959624774","data":{"timestamp":" 946959624773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959625427","data":{"timestamp":" 946959625427"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHELA"," userResponse":" MACHELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959628115","data":{"timestamp":" 946959628114"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMKUTA"," userResponse":" WALIMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959628608","data":{"timestamp":" 946959628607"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959628793","data":{"timestamp":" 946959628792"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959629512","data":{"timestamp":" 946959629511"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959630142","data":{"timestamp":" 946959630141"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959631587","data":{"timestamp":" 946959631586"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMECHAPWA"," userResponse":" AMECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959632050","data":{"timestamp":" 946959632049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959632683","data":{"timestamp":" 946959632683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUACHWA"," userResponse":" KUACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959633153","data":{"timestamp":" 946959633153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959633371","data":{"timestamp":" 946959633371"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959633954","data":{"timestamp":" 946959633953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959636848","data":{"timestamp":" 946959636847"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959637546","data":{"timestamp":" 946959637546"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959638895","data":{"timestamp":" 946959638894"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959639663","data":{"timestamp":" 946959639663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959640962","data":{"timestamp":" 946959640962"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959641327","data":{"timestamp":" 946959641327"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959641766","data":{"timestamp":" 946959641766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959642394","data":{"timestamp":" 946959642393"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959645566","data":{"timestamp":" 946959645565"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMZAWADI"," userResponse":" ALIMZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959646519","data":{"timestamp":" 946959646519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959646943","data":{"timestamp":" 946959646943"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959647930","data":{"timestamp":" 946959647929"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLIWAZA"," userResponse":" KUMLIWAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959651100","data":{"timestamp":" 946959651099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959652110","data":{"timestamp":" 946959652110"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959652367","data":{"timestamp":" 946959652367"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959652988","data":{"timestamp":" 946959652988"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959653998","data":{"timestamp":" 946959653998"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959654716","data":{"timestamp":" 946959654715"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959655316","data":{"timestamp":" 946959655315"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959656023","data":{"timestamp":" 946959656022"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959657091","data":{"timestamp":" 946959657091"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAIDIWA"," userResponse":" KUSAIDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959657944","data":{"timestamp":" 946959657943"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959658469","data":{"timestamp":" 946959658469"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959661072","data":{"timestamp":" 946959661070"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959661168","data":{"timestamp":" 946959661168"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" 41d097a2-889d-4f13-824b-72cddf07ac73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959678727","data":{"timestamp":" 946959678727"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959679622","data":{"timestamp":" 946959679621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959680264","data":{"timestamp":" 946959680264"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959680477","data":{"timestamp":" 946959680477"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959681169","data":{"timestamp":" 946959681168"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959681512","data":{"timestamp":" 946959681511"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959682014","data":{"timestamp":" 946959682013"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959685051","data":{"timestamp":" 946959685051"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959685373","data":{"timestamp":" 946959685373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959685986","data":{"timestamp":" 946959685985"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959687179","data":{"timestamp":" 946959687179"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAPENDANA"," userResponse":" TUNAPENDANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959687951","data":{"timestamp":" 946959687951"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959690825","data":{"timestamp":" 946959690825"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITUMWA"," userResponse":" TUKITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959691787","data":{"timestamp":" 946959691787"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959692569","data":{"timestamp":" 946959692569"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959695447","data":{"timestamp":" 946959695447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959695889","data":{"timestamp":" 946959695889"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959696733","data":{"timestamp":" 946959696733"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILITUMWA"," userResponse":" NILITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959697345","data":{"timestamp":" 946959697345"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959697498","data":{"timestamp":" 946959697498"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959697972","data":{"timestamp":" 946959697972"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959698364","data":{"timestamp":" 946959698364"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959699997","data":{"timestamp":" 946959699997"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKANUNUE"," userResponse":" NIKANUNUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959700769","data":{"timestamp":" 946959700769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959701282","data":{"timestamp":" 946959701282"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959701996","data":{"timestamp":" 946959701996"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959704791","data":{"timestamp":" 946959704791"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIENDA"," userResponse":" NILIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959705034","data":{"timestamp":" 946959705034"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959705567","data":{"timestamp":" 946959705567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959708408","data":{"timestamp":" 946959708408"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIWA"," userResponse":" TUKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959709351","data":{"timestamp":" 946959709351"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959710477","data":{"timestamp":" 946959710476"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIWAONA"," userResponse":" TULIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959711077","data":{"timestamp":" 946959711077"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959711956","data":{"timestamp":" 946959711955"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZETU"," userResponse":" WENZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959713199","data":{"timestamp":" 946959713199"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959713731","data":{"timestamp":" 946959713731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959713914","data":{"timestamp":" 946959713914"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959714436","data":{"timestamp":" 946959714436"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959717171","data":{"timestamp":" 946959717171"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959718535","data":{"timestamp":" 946959718535"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILITAMANI"," userResponse":" NILITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959719180","data":{"timestamp":" 946959719179"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959719813","data":{"timestamp":" 946959719812"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959720397","data":{"timestamp":" 946959720396"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959720580","data":{"timestamp":" 946959720579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959723543","data":{"timestamp":" 946959723542"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISEMA"," userResponse":" NILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959724347","data":{"timestamp":" 946959724346"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AH"," userResponse":" AH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959727764","data":{"timestamp":" 946959727763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959731303","data":{"timestamp":" 946959731302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959731841","data":{"timestamp":" 946959731841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959733085","data":{"timestamp":" 946959733085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959733837","data":{"timestamp":" 946959733837"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUWAOMBE"," userResponse":" TUWAOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959734451","data":{"timestamp":" 946959734451"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959734854","data":{"timestamp":" 946959734854"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAO"," userResponse":" NAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959735796","data":{"timestamp":" 946959735796"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959738197","data":{"timestamp":" 946959738197"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959738850","data":{"timestamp":" 946959738850"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" HUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959739463","data":{"timestamp":" 946959739462"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959739676","data":{"timestamp":" 946959739676"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959740368","data":{"timestamp":" 946959740368"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959743275","data":{"timestamp":" 946959743274"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959744298","data":{"timestamp":" 946959744298"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALINIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959745411","data":{"timestamp":" 946959745411"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959745893","data":{"timestamp":" 946959745893"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959746747","data":{"timestamp":" 946959746747"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959747500","data":{"timestamp":" 946959747499"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959747993","data":{"timestamp":" 946959747993"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TURUDI"," userResponse":" TURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959748616","data":{"timestamp":" 946959748616"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959751764","data":{"timestamp":" 946959751763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959752616","data":{"timestamp":" 946959752616"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959753100","data":{"timestamp":" 946959753100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959754224","data":{"timestamp":" 946959754224"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUCHEZE"," userResponse":" TUCHEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959754786","data":{"timestamp":" 946959754786"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959755278","data":{"timestamp":" 946959755278"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959757962","data":{"timestamp":" 946959757962"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIENDA"," userResponse":" TUKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959758773","data":{"timestamp":" 946959758773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959759512","data":{"timestamp":" 946959759511"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959760824","data":{"timestamp":" 946959760824"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATATURUHUSU"," userResponse":" HATATURUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959764503","data":{"timestamp":" 946959764503"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUBALIWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUBALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959764706","data":{"timestamp":" 946959764706"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959765558","data":{"timestamp":" 946959765558"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZETU"," userResponse":" WENZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959766760","data":{"timestamp":" 946959766760"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKACHEZA"," userResponse":" TUKACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959767323","data":{"timestamp":" 946959767323"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959770452","data":{"timestamp":" 946959770451"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa golikipa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959771483","data":{"timestamp":" 946959771482"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa golikipa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLIKIPA"," userResponse":" GOLIKIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959775725","data":{"timestamp":" 946959775724"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJITAHIDI"," userResponse":" NILIJITAHIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959776508","data":{"timestamp":" 946959776508"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUDAKA"," userResponse":" KUDAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959777110","data":{"timestamp":" 946959777110"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959779820","data":{"timestamp":" 946959779820"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZANGU"," userResponse":" WENZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959780773","data":{"timestamp":" 946959780773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959781367","data":{"timestamp":" 946959781367"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUNGA"," userResponse":" KUFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959781841","data":{"timestamp":" 946959781841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959782544","data":{"timestamp":" 946959782544"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959783006","data":{"timestamp":" 946959783006"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959786005","data":{"timestamp":" 946959786005"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959787358","data":{"timestamp":" 946959787358"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIOCHEZEA"," userResponse":" TULIOCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959788551","data":{"timestamp":" 946959788551"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959788775","data":{"timestamp":" 946959788775"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959789597","data":{"timestamp":" 946959789597"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGA"," userResponse":" MCHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959790739","data":{"timestamp":" 946959790739"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGI"," userResponse":" MWINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959793394","data":{"timestamp":" 946959793394"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGOLI"," userResponse":" MAGOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959794156","data":{"timestamp":" 946959794156"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959794760","data":{"timestamp":" 946959794760"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959795343","data":{"timestamp":" 946959795343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959796195","data":{"timestamp":" 946959796195"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959798981","data":{"timestamp":" 946959798980"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959799193","data":{"timestamp":" 946959799193"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959800060","data":{"timestamp":" 946959800059"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHEZO"," userResponse":" MCHEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959801116","data":{"timestamp":" 946959801115"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959801921","data":{"timestamp":" 946959801921"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959802720","data":{"timestamp":" 946959802720"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959803393","data":{"timestamp":" 946959803393"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUWA"," userResponse":" HATUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959803587","data":{"timestamp":" 946959803587"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959804140","data":{"timestamp":" 946959804139"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959806994","data":{"timestamp":" 946959806994"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANZA"," userResponse":" NILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959807978","data":{"timestamp":" 946959807978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959810784","data":{"timestamp":" 946959810783"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959812078","data":{"timestamp":" 946959812078"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKEMEA"," userResponse":" ALINIKEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959813073","data":{"timestamp":" 946959813073"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ACHA"," userResponse":" ACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959813556","data":{"timestamp":" 946959813556"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959815598","data":{"timestamp":" 946959815598"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959816052","data":{"timestamp":" 946959816052"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959816765","data":{"timestamp":" 946959816765"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITAKA"," userResponse":" ULITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959817359","data":{"timestamp":" 946959817358"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUCHEZE"," userResponse":" TUCHEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959817901","data":{"timestamp":" 946959817901"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959818055","data":{"timestamp":" 946959818054"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959818438","data":{"timestamp":" 946959818438"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959819091","data":{"timestamp":" 946959819090"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959821923","data":{"timestamp":" 946959821922"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIRUDI"," userResponse":" TULIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959822895","data":{"timestamp":" 946959822895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959823248","data":{"timestamp":" 946959823248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959824073","data":{"timestamp":" 946959824072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959824835","data":{"timestamp":" 946959824835"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959825748","data":{"timestamp":" 946959825748"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959828403","data":{"timestamp":" 946959828403"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959829646","data":{"timestamp":" 946959829646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMECHAFUKA"," userResponse":" TUMECHAFUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959830308","data":{"timestamp":" 946959830308"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959830752","data":{"timestamp":" 946959830752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959834031","data":{"timestamp":" 946959834031"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMKUTA"," userResponse":" TULIMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959834485","data":{"timestamp":" 946959834485"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959836097","data":{"timestamp":" 946959836097"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" AMEKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959836540","data":{"timestamp":" 946959836540"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959838886","data":{"timestamp":" 946959838885"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALI"," userResponse":" SWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959839018","data":{"timestamp":" 946959839018"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959839511","data":{"timestamp":" 946959839511"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959840534","data":{"timestamp":" 946959840534"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALITUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959841218","data":{"timestamp":" 946959841218"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959842481","data":{"timestamp":" 946959842481"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKUWA"," userResponse":" MMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959842933","data":{"timestamp":" 946959842933"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959843336","data":{"timestamp":" 946959843336"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959843479","data":{"timestamp":" 946959843479"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959844612","data":{"timestamp":" 946959844612"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959848255","data":{"timestamp":" 946959848255"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959848688","data":{"timestamp":" 946959848688"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959849752","data":{"timestamp":" 946959849752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOTEZA"," userResponse":" TULIPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959850425","data":{"timestamp":" 946959850425"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959851908","data":{"timestamp":" 946959851908"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959853722","data":{"timestamp":" 946959853721"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASAMEHE"," userResponse":" NAWASAMEHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959853984","data":{"timestamp":" 946959853984"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959855248","data":{"timestamp":" 946959855248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959856095","data":{"timestamp":" 946959856094"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIRUDIE"," userResponse":" MSIRUDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959856629","data":{"timestamp":" 946959856629"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959857663","data":{"timestamp":" 946959857663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959858076","data":{"timestamp":" 946959858076"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959858640","data":{"timestamp":" 946959858640"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUHUSA"," userResponse":" RUHUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959861804","data":{"timestamp":" 946959861804"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959862548","data":{"timestamp":" 946959862548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959863471","data":{"timestamp":" 946959863471"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALISHA"," userResponse":" KUWALISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959863915","data":{"timestamp":" 946959863915"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959864098","data":{"timestamp":" 946959864097"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959864530","data":{"timestamp":" 946959864530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959867786","data":{"timestamp":" 946959867786"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959868858","data":{"timestamp":" 946959868858"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIOGA"," userResponse":" TULIOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959869051","data":{"timestamp":" 946959869051"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959869445","data":{"timestamp":" 946959869444"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959870517","data":{"timestamp":" 946959870517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAFI"," userResponse":" WASAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959873175","data":{"timestamp":" 946959873174"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959873241","data":{"timestamp":" 946959873241"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" ce9e6995-1245-4f54-a824-0adc5a03c923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAFI"," userResponse":" WASAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959884284","data":{"timestamp":" 946959884283"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959887713","data":{"timestamp":" 946959887713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959889260","data":{"timestamp":" 946959889260"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959892221","data":{"timestamp":" 946959892221"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959893769","data":{"timestamp":" 946959893769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959895680","data":{"timestamp":" 946959895680"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959897225","data":{"timestamp":" 946959897224"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959901197","data":{"timestamp":" 946959901196"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959902755","data":{"timestamp":" 946959902755"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959905819","data":{"timestamp":" 946959905819"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959907385","data":{"timestamp":" 946959907385"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959908176","data":{"timestamp":" 946959908175"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_064714"," gameId":" b1bef355-06fa-4d00-8c0a-c55396ca8420"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}